Guide to the Galerie Jacques Benador Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Artwork, 1952-1970, undated; Series V; 2.33; (1 container)
  - Gen Paul: color drawing of Jacques Benador, 1953 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Bram van Velde: lithographs, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Bran van Velde: four lithographs dedicated to Jacques Benador, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Bran van Velde: four lithographs dedicated to Jacques Benador, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Bran van Velde: four lithographs dedicated to Jacques Benador, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Bran van Velde: four lithographs dedicated to Jacques Benador, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))